fishisfast.com 2011-03-04

# Fishisfast Electronics - Privacy

We won't sell your information to anyone, ever. We will only contact you regarding an order placed with us or an inquiry you may have or if you decide to opt in to our mailing list. That's the short version. Here's the specifics:

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.   

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.  

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * To send periodic emails 
    * The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.  

    * If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.fishisfast.com/terms.html  

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.   

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

http://www.fishisfast.com  
5646 Commerce St. STE E2  
48911, MI 48911  
United States  
service@fishisfast.com  
1.517.877.893.4535
